AMANDA FEBRIYANI

Student

☎: 081273611047, **☎**: amandafebriyani2001@gmail.com

• Indonesia, North Sumatra, cover road no 10, Medan, North Sumatra.

D.O.B: 09/29/2001

Gender: Female

Marital Status: Single

Nationality: Indonesia

SUMMARY

Experienced Accountant and Graphic Designer with over one year of experience in the industry. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements. Consistently saved costs while increasing profits. I am also skilled in Photoshop and logo design using Adobe Illustrator. Additionally, experienced in sales and marketing administration, where I handled order processing, sales recording, coordination with field teams, and payroll management for the team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Accountancy - PT Mikrotek Komputindo

Medan. Indonesia

November 2021 - April 2023

- Make office financial bookkeeping
- Make a financial report containing the company's financial recapitulation data that has been signed and will be submitted directly to the leadership.
- Verifying the completeness of the company's financial documents including checking receipts and invoices as well as invoices or notes, ensuring all documents are complete and storing them neatly

Graphic Desain - PT Mikrotek Komputindo

Medan, Indonesia

- November 2021 April 2023
- Make a concept of information and materials related to the design to be done
- Integrating elements of art, visuals, and language in a design to convey a message
- Make designs that are communicative and easy to understand

Sales and Marketing Admin-PT Universal Indofood Product

Medan, Indonesia

Oktober 2023 – Present

- Process Product request from distributors and coordinate with the factory
- · Record and summarize monthly and annual sales data
- Effectively coordinate with field team in the designated areas.

(Teknik Informartika)	- Bachelor Of Engineering	
Medan, Indonesia.		September 2021 – Till Date
CVILLE		
SKILLS		
Adobe Photoshop	Web Developer	Adobe Ilustrator
Microsoft Office		
Microsoft Office HOBBIES		
HOBBIES	Create A Design With Adobe Photosh	nop and Adobe Ilustrator

EDUCATION

Available on Request